tower.com 2008-12-16

# Security and Privacy Policy at Tower.com

|   
---  
|    
---  

| 

## Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
Effective date: May 18th, 2007

Tower.com's Commitment to Safe Internet Shopping

We offer 128-bit SSL encryption, which encrypts your personal and credit card information as it is transferred over the Internet. 

We electronically verify each order with the credit company at the moment it is placed, returning an order confirmed message only if the issuing bank authorizes it. Our experienced staff then manually checks all orders which still appear unusual, canceling any we feel are not valid.

In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, federal law states that you will not be liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. Tower.com will cover this liability, up to $50, as long as the following is true:

  1. You have reported the fraudulent use to the issuing bank of your credit card according to their reporting rules and procedures. 
  2. The unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own. 
  3. The credit card number was obtained from purchases made at Tower.com while using our secure server.

Return to the Top  

## Cookies  
  
---  
  
Cookies are small files with basic information we use to enhance your browsing and shopping experience on the Tower.com site. Many major e-commerce web sites, including Tower.com, require the use of cookies to shop on their sites. Cookies are not harmful to your computer and cannot be used to retrieve personal information, install a virus, or get your email address. We use cookies to: 

  * Keep track of items in your shopping bag during current and future visits to Tower.com 
  * Remember information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Tower.com site 
  * Speed navigation 
  * Provide you with custom tailored content 
  * Monitor the effectiveness of our marketing email campaigns 
  * Monitor total number of visitors, pages viewed and other aggregate metrics 
  * Track your entries, submissions and status in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests 

Cookies need to be enabled to shop at Tower.com. To enable cookies on your browser, please refer to the instructions for your specific browser below. To find the current version of your browser, click "Help" at the top of your browser and then select "About."

Internet Explorer 6.x

  1. On the Tools menu, click Internet Options.
  2. Click the Privacy tab.
  3. Click Advanced.
  4. Click Override Automatic Cookie Handling.
  5. Check Accept under First Party Cookies.
  6. Check Always Allow Session Cookies.
  7. Click OK.
  8. Close and restart your browser.

Internet Explorer 5.x (Windows)

  1. On the Tools menu, click Internet Options.
  2. Click the Security tab.
  3. Click the web content zone you want to set cookie options for. (For more information about web content zones, see Internet Explorer Help.)
  4. Click the Custom Level button.
  5. Scroll down to the Cookies section.
  6. Check both "Enable" radio buttons.
  7. Click OK.
  8. Close and restart your browser.

Internet Explorer 5.x (Mac)

  1. On the Explorer menu, click Preferences.
  2. Scroll down to the Receiving Files section in the left navigation bar.
  3. Select Cookies in the left navigation bar.
  4. Select Never Ask in the When Receiving Files drop-down list.
  5. Click OK.
  6. Close and restart your browser.

Netscape Navigator 6.x  

  1. On the Edit menu, click Preferences.
  2. Click the Privacy & Security arrow.
  3. Click the Cookies sub-category.
  4. Check the Enable Cookies radio button.
  5. Click OK.
  6. Close and restart your browser.

Mozilla 1.x  

  1. On the Edit menu, click Preferences.
  2. Expand Privacy & Security in the left navigation bar.
  3. Click Cookies in the left navigation bar.
  4. Check the "Allow all cookies" radio button.
  5. Click OK.
  6. Close and restart your browser.

Firefox 1.x

  1. On the Tools menu, click Options.
  2. Select Privacy in the left navigation bar.
  3. Expand the cookies section.
  4. Check the "Allow Sites to Set Cookies" checkbox.
  5. Click OK.
  6. Close and restart your browser.

Safari 1.x

  1. On the Safari menu, click Preferences.
  2. Select Security in the top navigation bar.
  3. Check the "Always" radio button in the "Accept Cookies" section.
  4. Click Close.
  5. Close and restart your browser.

Return to the Top  

## Log Files  
  
---  
  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. A third party may set cookies on our site (used for the same purpose as log files); however, cookies are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Return to the Top  

## Your Personal Information  
  
---  
  
  * What personal information do we collect?  

  * How is your personal information used?  

  * Who is collecting your personal information?  

  * With whom is your personal information shared?  

  * How can I access, update or delete my personal information?  

  * How does Tower.com protect your personal information?  

  * What kind of security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information?  

  * What else you should know about your online privacy?  

  * Notification of Changes

Your privacy is important to us. Tower.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties. We will only share your personal information with third parties for the purposes that are disclosed within this privacy policy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings.

What personal information do we collect?

You will be asked to provide your first and last name, email, billing and shipping addresses during registration. 

If you contact Tower.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Occasionally we ask users to complete surveys used for research purposes to improve and enhance Tower.com. Wherever Tower.com collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to our Privacy Policy.

Return to Questions

How does Tower.com use my information?  
The primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with personalized services and interactive communications, which allows you to check order status. Your personal information also allows us to email you newsletters customized to your individual music and entertainment tastes.

Who is collecting information?  
When providing personal information to Tower.com, you are sharing that information with Tower.com alone. 

With whom does Tower.com share my information?  
Tower.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We will not disclose your personal information except under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Return to Questions

How can I access, update or delete my personal information?  
You may edit your Tower.com Account information at any time by signing in to your account and clicking "Update Account." Here you can access, review and update your personal information. Your Tower.com Account can be deleted, but doing so will result in not being able to access any members-only areas of Tower.com. To delete your account, please email us at [feedback@tower.com](mailto:feedback@tower.com) from the email address attached to your account. Include specific instruction to delete your account.

Return to Questions

How does Tower.com protect my personal information?  
We use state-of-the-art technology to safeguard your personal information. All Tower.com employees are required to acknowledge that they understand and will comply with this privacy policy. Employees who violate this policy will be subjected to disciplinary action, up to, and including termination.

Return to Questions

What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?  
Tower.com takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely. We use 128 bit encryption when transmitting your information to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We strive to protect your personal information while in transmission or when it is stored on our systems, however, Tower.com cannot ensure or warrant the security or services. 

What else should I know about my privacy?  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (message boards, email, chat areas, etc.) - that information can be collected and used by others. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

Return to Questions

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Return to the Top  

## Still Have Questions? TALK TO US!  
  
---  
  
Email:  

For US and Canadian Customers: 1-800-ASK-TOWER (1-800-275-8693)  
For International Customers: +1-514-315-9145  
All Telephone Support available Monday-Friday 9:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m. PST  

|   
  
---  

**Copyright © 1995 - 2008 TOWER.COM INC.**  
Tower, Tower Records, TowerRecords.com, Tower.com, Tower CD Listening Station, Tower Outlet, Tower Records Videos Books, Tower Essentials, Pulse! and associated logos and trademarks are registered trademarks of Tower.com Inc. in the United States and other countries.  
Copyright 2007 Powered by Muze Inc. For personal noncommercial use only.   
  
To link directly to this page: http://www.tower.com/help/help_security.cfm  
  
Tower 2.0 Version 3.8.7
